Yeah, man. I just finishing up my uh
18th report and uh and then I I've got
to submit six more and I'm like, "Shut
the freak up, Brandon."
>> Oh, man. Was it the accent or the bug
count that annoyed you when I saw?
>> You know, a little bit of both, you
know. Makes me feel like I'm in the bin,
you know?
>> Best part of when you can just, you
know, critical think, right?
Yeah, dude.
[Music]
>> All righty, hackers. Fun little
announcement before we jump into the
episode this week. Um, Brandon Gret me,
you know, you guys know him and love him
from the pod. Has been working with us
for a long time. He's been running our
hacker notes. Um, and he's done an
excellent job at that. But after
probably two years of working with the
pod, we have decided to graduate him to
a co-host in light of his massive
success in the bug bounty world lately
in the live hacking events um and just
going as a full-time hunter. Uh I think
we'd like to have him a little bit more
in the spotlight and sharing his
experiences. So Reszo isn't going
anywhere. Don't worry, I'm not going
anywhere. We will have three hosts to
the podcast, yours truly, Reszo, and
Gret. um and we will kind of hand off
from week to week, but uh I just I just
it's just been amazing to see his growth
as a hacker and I think he brings really
good insights to the pod. Um so we just
wanted to welcome him on as a co-host.
Um so yeah, shoot him a DM, tell him you
love him. He's he's doing a great job
and I'm excited to chat with him each
week. Uh actually, I think this episode
that we're running right now should have
him on it. So uh enjoy and uh yeah,
definitely send him some love. All
right, let's go.
All right, hackers. We got a quick This
Week in Bug Bounty segment for you this
time around. Um, it's kind of actually
been a big week for Yes We Hack. They
just landed an $8 million contract with
the European Commission uh becoming the
new preferred bug bounty services uh
provider in the EU. Um and I think these
sort of things as long uh in addition to
what's going on in Iceland with their
program um the European Union we're
seeing uh they're making moves in the
bug bounty world and uh I really want
that to be successful because then other
parts of the world will learn from it
and do the same. So um very interesting
stuff here. Yes We Hack also recently
became a uh CNA which is cool. Um so
they can issue CVES a and they launched
this is the opportunity I wanted to tell
you guys about. they launched this uh
opensource uh bug bounty uh leaderboard
here. Um there are already quite a few
people rocking it on here, but if you're
really into the open source scene, this
could be a great place to look, find
other hackers to collaborate with and
programs to work on. All right, let's go
back to the show.
Dude, these these are the weeks that we
live for, man. Am I right? Like these
live hacking events bring I just leave
these live hacking events just brimming
with with energy and passion for Bug
Bounty.
>> Oh man, it is so good. It's so good. You
get to see your friends. You get to
hopefully completely crush the target
and have some good war stories from it.
It is top tier stuff. You just can't you
can't top it.
>> Yeah, dude. Okay, so let's set the scene
a little bit here. Um I just got back
from Sweden with the Hacker One Live
hacking event. Awesome. You are
currently crushing it in an IPC with uh
is the target public for those or no?
>> I don't know. I'm not sure.
>> How many reports, dude? It's like 20
something reports, right?
>> So, I checked the stats this morning. I
spoke with JRock and he was like, man,
you're responsible for half of the total
reported reports.
>> That's my boy. Yes. Well done, man.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I I I because we had our little,
you know, I don't even we we used to
call it our mentorship meeting. Now
you've kind of graduated from this, but
we had our little sync meeting and uh
and you were like, "Yeah, you know, and
I started one day one one freaking day
late on this competition, man." And
you're like, "Yeah, man. I just
finishing up my uh 18th report." And uh
and then I I've got to submit six more.
And I'm like, "Shut the freak up,
Brandon."
>> Was it the accent or the bug count that
annoyed you when I saw?
>> You know, a little bit of both, you
know, just makes me feel like I'm in the
bin, you know. Um, no dude, but that's
exciting, right? And so I mean what how
how, bro?
>> Yeah, I done a little bit of prep before
the event to help myself out because
it's been a while since I have actually
committed some time to hunting. So,
>> a week before I really got into the
event headsp space, I sort of done what
I could do around getting my
information about some of the services
that could have been in scope. I didn't
know at the time.
>> Um, and I started looking around at the
scope when it drops. And I really I have
this I don't know theory of like know
your target is what I refer to it as
when I'm trying to explain it. And I try
and summarize
what would hurt and where would hurt and
based on what scope is available, what I
can do with that. So essentially what Oh
man, I'm really trying hard not to like
give any details cuz
>> Come on, man. Like give give us a little
juice. Just a tiny little bit of juice.
Well,
I
was fortunate enough to use a bug to
gain some information
from another part of the app. And
although the bugs aren't chained, the
information was quite useful because I
could deduct
a lot from what I had.
>> Um,
say no more. That is it.
I see. Okay. So, this is a little bit
more this is a little a little shout to
the bug bount metagaming here, which is
like
>> when you are finding vulnerabilities and
gadgets as well, you know, gadgets that
can leak information, but um you got to
keep a big picture mentality here,
right? It's not necessarily like you are
>> always just going to find the bug,
report the bug, and then it's fresh
slate and you move to the next one,
right? Sometimes you can use what you
learn from those bugs or use some of the
information revealed via those bugs to
inform other vulnerabilities and and in
fact you should if you're looking to
optimize your earnings, right? Is that
what you're saying?
>> Yeah, absolutely. And I just really dug
deep, tried to understand the threat
model, tried to understand all of the
apps and uh sort of got a got a bit of a
feel for what I would perform well on.
And that's another thing as well when
you're looking at scope and you're
trying to get a feel for it.
try and look for your flavors of hunting
on that scope and see because I doubled
down. I was like, "Okay, I probably
would do okay here." And I was right
this time.
>> And dude, I also done a collab with the
with the with the big dogs as well.
>> Well, with Oh, did you really? Okay.
>> Yeah, with the big dogs. So, that's
that's going to be a fun one if it comes
through, but
>> Well, I think you messaged me, right?
Can I don't know if I can dox your DMs
here, but like you messaged me and
you're like, "Hey, man. I've got this
cool thing." And then like I see like
two hours later I didn't wasn't at my
phone. You're go like [__] you know,
Fron popped it. It's like it's like ah
dang it, you know, like
>> um what was interesting I kept that
conversation going or we kept that
conversation going and we actually
figured out we could do some other
things on another end point. Um so we
got a really nice bug out of that as
well. So yeah, it's good. But that's
Sorry. I I just I I wanted to say just
going back to before we moved along from
your principle that you shared just a
second ago. I totally think that's true
and trying to align the scope to your um
like capabilities and stuff like that
and figure out which app in scope is
like you know you have an advantage on
as a hunter. But one of the things that
I've, you know, just consistently come
back to lately is, um, you know, I am
intimidated by a good amount of scope
like desktop applications, binaries,
some mobile stuff, um, you know, like
just there's a good amount of that that
I am afraid of.
>> And then sometimes I try to go after
that because that's where the impact is
and I can see that clearly. And I always
am happy that I did that, you know, like
I I I have never not been happy that
I've done that. And I just think that's
really odd because I feel like I should
fail at that sometimes, you know, and I
feel like I should come out with like,
ah, this is a little bit of a hit or
miss, you know, like uh but really every
single time I've done it, it's been
like, wow, that was great, you know?
>> Yeah. I remember you saying that about a
few events actually. I feel like
there's two things that come into play,
though. is really understanding the
threat model and also having a good
foundation to rely on in terms of
technical ability because there are a
lot of principles and concepts which
will be crosslicable regardless of what
you're looking at and I feel like you
obviously have very very strong
foundations to tap into. So just look at
whatever man you'll find bugs you'll be
fine.
>> It could be it could be it could be
that. Yeah. But I also think a lot of
other hackers are intimidated by the
same things you're likely intimidated
by. Sure. and you know they you they
probably haven't had eyes on it. And
actually this is something that I was
thinking about recently. Um and I was on
a run and I was thinking actually about
um you know your conversation about
starting your your pentest company or
whatever because you've had a lot of
inbound and I was thinking you know one
of the really cool things that I would
like to see some people market um in a
pentest company is a pentest company
that only looks at the intimidating part
of your scope.
>> Right? So this is not your first pentest
company. This is the company that is
going to go deep and get the things that
other people shied away from because
they have a responsibility to do
coverage on other parts of the apps,
right? Um and and so like let's talk
about a normal pentest situation. You
know, you hire a company, they come in,
you've got 80 hours to do the pentest.
60 hours, 70 hours is, oh, I need to
cover all of the web endpoints and I
need to like check them for all of the
normal stuff and, you know, some logic
bugs or whatever, right? That takes up
the bulk of your time and then, you
know, you have maybe 10, 15 hours to
look for these crazy deep bugs, right?
Not enough.
>> Not enough, right? And so, they don't do
it. And then, okay, you're like, okay, I
fix some of those things. Well, guess
what? the next guys that are going to do
the next pen test, they've got to go
through and they've got to do their due
diligence on those same applications,
those same endpoints, right? And and you
know, maybe they'll find something
different because they've got a
different set of eyes and a different
way of perceiving those pieces of
functionality, but it's unlikely that
anybody is going through all of the
hoops to configure all the stuff like we
see in Bug Bounty, right? Like that's
what why we find crazy stuff in Bug
Bounty is because we are digging deeper
deeper and we're not confined by this by
a need to cover everything because we
can cover whatever the heck we want,
>> right?
>> Um and and I think it it would be a
really interesting differentiator for a
pentest company to say, "Hey, listen,
we're going to ignore all of the basic
scope. Some give it to the other pentest
companies, okay? We are just gonna go
for the stuff that's very deep and very
technical in your app and and you know
spend time there and we may not find
anything but we may find something that
breaks the whole world you know
>> for sure. So sort of like a flavor of
red teaming but for web apps and that
sort of hardcore like in the weeds type
research.
>> Yeah.
>> I think it could be very good and and we
see some of this stuff with like Cure 53
and stuff like that, right? Where
they're they're going super deep on
stuff. But I I I don't know that they're
putting it in their marketing material
that it's like, "Hey, listen. We're not
going to find your access control bugs,
>> you know, like it's not going to happen.
We're gonna focus on
>> this, you know."
>> Yeah. No, that's an interesting thought.
I feel like there would be a lot of
appetite as well for some of the bigger
security companies
>> that want that to
go through their budget to improve and
also for actual bug bounty companies as
well before adding new scope. it too in
program. That's exactly what they had
want to do.
>> Let's let's talk about that after.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Like why why are we doing
this on air? [__] Um Yeah. Okay. All
right. Um anyway, let's get to the
actual content of the Oh, wait. No, no,
no. I didn't even get to talk about my
live hacking event.
>> Yeah. So, how how did your stuff go? I
heard from somewhere you might have done
very well from this.
>> Yeah, dude. Frick. I Let me check right
now because I think they're still paying
out some of the stuff. I'm still as of
the recording this in first place just
barely sliding above the uh the team
baguette
>> French guys. Um which is amazing. Um
>> but yeah man it was a great event. Um
this one was in Sweden which is actually
one of my top places in the world to go.
And um I I found a couple um good bugs
that I was actually able to get
escalated to criticals because of um
some nuances in their threat model. Um
that would not traditionally be
criticals. Um and so that was good. And
then yeah, man, just sat down and pumped
pumped it out on a very difficult piece
of scope and found, you know, the the
super crit that that you need to like
seal a good event, right? Because I feel
like um you know just going back to the
live hacking event strategy thing, I
feel like if you want to crush it at an
event, you got to have like good
performance across the board. You know,
get your mediums in there, get your
highs in there, get get, you know, one
crit, two crits, and then one mega crit,
right? That kind of seals the deal at
least. You know, if you get one mega
crit that's like, oh no, like this is
the end of the world, then that that
really solidifies the event for you. So
that's what I was going for.
>> So I wanted to talk to you about that
because there's this I've had it in a
few of the other events when I'm really
digging deep to try and find something
obscure or it's taking me a bunch of
time.
>> I enter
panic's not the right word, but like
this mindset of oh no, I'm not reporting
something. Do I do I go for volume or do
I go deep in this? Do you experience
that at all? And how do you combat that?
because it it almost blocks my ability
to go really deep in the weeds sometimes
and it's very frustrating.
>> Yeah, I think it I think I do and I
think that was I that was something I
struggled with more earlier in my life
hacking event career
>> but still struggle with and that is why
you know in the beginning I spent a lot
of time and just like you did this event
I was so hyped when I heard you say this
because I'm like that's that's my guy.
Um but you know going for volume trying
to get a feel of these applications
right um getting a decent amount of base
reports in and then you you've already
done you know a good amount of uh you
know like looking into a specific app
right and and I would say volume in a in
a specific app like I would really not
endorse jumping from app to app to app
volume and a specific app
>> and then and then you know after the
dupe window closes or after you feel
like you got a base of reports or
understandings, then kind of shooting
your shot for those deeper those deeper
bugs, right? Um,
>> yeah,
>> but yeah, I I think I often I've done
that post dupe window. The con of this
approach is that sometimes the mega
crits that people find right off the bat
will get fixed and you'll miss them,
>> you know. Yeah, I mean it's again
finding a strategy that works for you
fundamentally because different people
like there's a few LH hackers that run
their game in a way which would just
give me a meltdown when I can't do this.
>> Um so again I think it just comes back
to as you said that experience and
finding your flow because everyone looks
for different bug classes. different bug
classes require varying context of the
application varying understand and it's
all unique I guess is my point
>> it is it is man it's a it's a very
unique ecosystem it's a good it's a good
thing that we've got variety too and and
I think some hackers just don't give a
lily and they show up and they hack
whatever they want to hack and I think
that's cool you know uh but I think
>> yeah and and and to some degree I aspire
to that but I also aspire to really
consistently performing at these live
hacking events And I think um that my
methodology and the methodology you
implemented here I think is one of the
most reliable ways to reliably perform.
Right. And yeah and whereas you'll see
some people that knock knock mega crits
on day two at some events and then don't
find anything at other events.
>> Yeah. 100%. I feel like we might have to
edit that out because that's a very
valuable meta strategy.
>> Yeah.
>> That people are going to use against us.
>> Yeah. Well, you know, hey, that's that's
the give and take of the pod, man. Like,
I I especially lately I've been
realizing like, dang. Like, some of the
stuff that I that we distribute on the
pod stings sometimes when it comes back
to to to like be used against you in a
competition,
>> dude. The one of my most prized gadgets
that I use in so many chains that I
mentioned on my first pod episode
>> has been patched since that went out.
And I only noticed this like two weeks
ago. What is it?
>> Maybe three weeks ago. Um it was the
>> on the target that I look at quite often
in a certain part of their ecosystem,
the OAF um
>> mode where you can force a redirect.
>> Yeah.
>> Just without sort of like it's just by
design, but they patched it and it
completely
>> I was getting so excited. I thought I've
got something just for this and then
nothing. I was like
>> I shouldn't have said it on the F. I
just should have just left it. Yeah.
Yeah. And and sometimes and like we
discussed before this episode, you know,
you do have to kind of watch the things
you say because these companies do like
especially the companies that we're
talking about under you know I guess
behind the scenes a little bit right now
all they all listen to the podcast you
know and so it's like all right but um
but yeah it's
>> it is it is and it and it's a part of
the give and take of the industry as
well. we are standing on the shoulders
of giants in so many ways, you know, um,
>> and so, yeah, I guess it's uh, it's part
of the game.
>> Before we move on, I did want to talk
about some of your takeaways because you
have some very unconventional pieces of
wisdom in here,
>> uh, which I'd like you to double double
click on.
>> So, I want to I want to be clear about
this. Um these takeaways are a mix of um
experiences from this last live hacking
event and from talking to other hackers
at the live hacking event about their
experiences at LHS and in hacking over
the past like couple couple weeks now um
or a couple months. I I want to disclaim
here. I always get people's permission
before I share these these things. So
don't you freickers come up to me and be
like, "Oh, can't tell Justin anything
because he's gonna yap about it on the
pod." I always get permission before I
talk about something on the pod. Um, so
anyway, with that being said, here are a
couple fun takeaways. Okay. Um, one,
sometimes you fight with a W, okay? And
that is a very unpleasant experience.
And most of the time we win our battles
with WS. Um, it's just persistence, it's
encodings, it's understanding quirks of
the system. uh it's, you know, stripping
or sanitization that occurs on the back
side of the WFT, right? All of those
things can lead you to bypassing WS. Uh
contextually aware WAFS as well, you
know, trying to abuse that. Um
yeah, the problem is sometimes they've
just got like a includes rule and they
just autodeny and it's like there's
nothing you can do, you know. Mhm.
>> Um and so one of the hackers I was
speaking with had a situation like this
uh recently and they were saying that
one the way that they actually ended up
uh exploiting it was internal employees
for this company are not routing through
the W. They DNS internally resolves to
directly to the host. So, um, while all
of the users of the company,
you know, were hitting Cloudflare or
Okami or whatever it was, um, when an
employee clicked to the link, it would
it there was no W in front of it and the
bug would pop, right? Um, and in the
specific context the guy was telling me
about, uh, it like the internal
employees were one of the prime targets
for this bug and they had a delivery
mechanism through the business logic,
right? So, it was just like perfect
storm and uh and but I I hadn't really
thought about that before. So, I wanted
to shout that out and I also just don't
have really any good ideas on how to
test whether this is possible without
actually like having a contact at the
company.
>> Yeah, it's tough because those sort of
context switches are what you'll only
really see when you're looking at say
like blind XSS bugs typically, isn't it?
because they're being detonated from a
different context
>> in terms of how man
>> you'd need some serious threat modeling
and guessing I think in order to get to
that and you'd also need the bugs to
line up in a sense that you actually can
deliver a canary of some description to
even test it.
>> So I'll say it's definitely rarer from
what I can think.
>> Yeah, I'm thinking as well like
blind XSS is is an interesting point.
You know, you could definitely test it
with a blind XSS. Um, if you're just
looking for if you have a blind XSS and
you are trying to do what you were
saying, like use the bug to gain more
information about your target, which is
a little bit red teamey, a little bit
pivoty, but you know, ask forgiveness
rather than permission there sometimes.
Um, and but I was also thinking when you
said that actually maybe this could be a
good use for blind SSRFs is if you've
got like a like a only status code blind
SSRF, what you could do is try to hit an
asset from that blind SSRF in uh, you
know, that's a public facing asset from
within the comp the company and it, you
know, put a malicious uh, string. Let's
just do like your normal script alert,
right?
>> In the query params. And if it hits that
server and doesn't give a 403, then
you're not getting blocked by the W,
right? Uh but if it does, then you know
that you are routing through the W.
>> Yeah. So interesting interesting thing.
You could potentially use a blind SSRF
to kind of give you some intel about the
company for.
>> That's good. That's good.
>> But that comes with its own caveats of
you don't actually know the segment you
are calling out from internally and what
that looks like. But it's still a
potential gadget nonetheless.
>> Yeah. It doesn't say that it it's not
the case, but if it works, then you do
know that it is the case.
>> Exactly. Exactly.
>> It's like a
>> Yeah, that's some big brain stuff.
>> That's like some I I know there's some
like logical like if A is B and B is C,
then A is C or whatever like thing that
I can do there, but I I I can't wrap my
head around it while I'm talking.
>> Yeah, don't look at me, mate. I I can't
do that on the spot either. Give me 10
minutes and I might be able to see.
Um okay so that's takeaway number one
circ can circumvent w sometimes um with
for internal employees not routing
through you know uh external DNS
um number two
secondary context bugs I've always
struggled with exploiting um and I've
done it you know a dozen couple dozen
times probably but I I just whenever I
look at them unless it's really verbose
and it's really just dumping back
exactly what's happening on the back end
um API. Sometimes I really struggle with
it because it's like um
like you know they're expecting a
certain format in the JSON structure of
their response and sometimes you're
getting partial fields back and
sometimes you're not getting anything
back and it's like um one one tip that I
did get from a hacker at this live
hacking event um and they actually
showed me the bug from a couple months
ago that they exploited was that
secondary context bugs um can also be
exploited to bypass pass access controls
within a like arbback environment which
is very interesting like sometimes what
you'll see in in apps is that um you
know they've got maybe like your
organization ID or your account ID or
whatever in the URL right and if you try
to mess with that at all you're done
you're cooked right that like it just
has to be there as a part of the path um
for the API and that's where all their
access controls are done um but
sometimes that's done by a front-end
service so if you have a secondary
context path traversal
>> um you you may be able to uh you know
provide a organization or an account ID
in the path that you own right so that
you're an admin on but then you're also
in in a different organization where
you're just a lower privilege user and
then overwrite that on the secondary on
the secondary context traverse back up
and then and then uh go build out the
whole path again I hope that makes sense
but um
>> you know I I almost always thought about
this from the context of like um
crossorg attacks and I think obviously
that's where you should go first but if
you're really stumped on crossorgs
attack definitely try to exploit um same
or arbback implementation uh and see
make sure that extends past the first
proxy
>> into the secondary API as well
>> that oh this is so painful because
there's so much I want to talk about but
I can't from this event but that exact
scenario is I'm
>> working with something now and I've been
testing this theory all morning. Um
hopefully I can talk about it next time.
But
>> yeah,
>> it's very good way to look at things
because once you start getting those
sort of gadgets, it can turn something
which was weird behavior into a really
really nice bug just by thinking about
architecturally where are those access
controls implemented. And if you can get
the biceer or something like that to
disclose that as well, which I may or
may not have done somewhere. Oh, just
I'm going to stop talking,
>> dude. Yeah, it's crazy because I mean
the the bug that the guy showed me it's
it's on a different target than the one
you're working on.
>> And it's interesting that
we're seeing this this when you know
you're giving good tips guys. This is
you know this is what's so exciting to
me about critical thinking though is I
love it when we get to talk about stuff
like this and I know that many top tier
hackers are listening to this being like
ah I'm going to change my methodology
because of this. You know, that's our
north star with critical thinking is and
even with you coming on as the as the
co-host, which by the way, after we
started, I decided I'm gonna record a
preempt to this episode and explain
that. So, okay, they already know about
that by now.
>> Okay, good. Um but uh yeah I mean it's
you know one of the north stars that for
the podcast is making sure that elite
hackers you know intermediate to
advanced level hackers are getting a
takeaway every single week that modifies
their methodology that makes them be a
better hacker. Right. If we're doing
just one of those every week then we're
winning, right?
>> Absolutely.
>> Um and so yeah.
>> Absolutely. Let's just hope we don't dup
on any of these bugs now.
>> Yeah, dude. Shucks. Yeah. Okay. Um, all
right, last one.
>> I'll keep this one brief.
>> I don't know. This is something that I I
mean, I was in Sweden, so I was hanging
out with with Fron and Matias, and these
guys are just legendary. And um, and I
always leave conversations with them
thinking like, man, I do not theorize
what's happening in the backend pip
pipelines
nearly as much as I should, you know?
And especially in an environment when
you're working with an amazing team and
and you can have a conversation with
them about like hey is this what's going
on in your back end or you know whatever
like um uh it just opens my eyes to like
oh yeah that is a very logical deduction
that I could have made from a blackbox
perspective and I just need to start
flexing those muscles a little bit more.
>> That is exactly it. I recall there was a
time at some point last year when I
messaged you after France dropped a
crazy bug and I was like what have you
done this week
>> to think more like France when you're
approaching a target and I remember
messaging you like four times but yeah I
think he's the best example of it when
the research on the do you remember the
headers when he like shelled through the
ident
>> through the request ID the like logging
headers yeah
>> that is like the perfect research If you
haven't seen it, go and check out the
old hacker notes because that is like
the perfect highlight of using that.
What can we deduct from a blackbox
scenario
perfect of exactly that and it's just
insane.
>> One of the one of the things I've
realized from this too from from talking
to Fran and Matias though is that like
Matias is so I mean we I've highlighted
Matias many times on this podcast
because of the amazing hacker that he
is, but he continues to be underrated
man. Like Matias is is every bit like as
as good at that as Fron is and and you
just don't hear about it quite as much.
So
>> I feel like he doesn't make as much
content though compared I might be wrong
on that.
>> We're fixing that though. We are like I
I've I sent him a mic for the pod like
and and to be honest man I've used his
Archive Alchemist tool a bunch. We
talked about on the pod. He covered it
in an episode. super good tool and
really really excellent for finding
critical vulnerabilities. And guys, like
if you haven't watched that episode, go
back and watch that episode. Whenever
you're you actually have the opportunity
to test an archive upload, okay? because
um I did that recently when I was
testing some stuff and I had such a
blast with it and I got some really
impactful stuff out of it and um now I
feel excuse me so much more comfortable
with that tool, you know, and I've got
muscle memory for it. I know exactly
what it can do and and now that I've
done it at least once testing the whole
methodology that he outlined in that
episode, I just feel like I've got a
grip on it now and I will not shy away
at all from archive related
vulnerabilities moving forward. I will
run to them, you know, because I've got
the tool and the methodology to to
exploit them.
>> Yeah, man. I've been waiting. I really
have been waiting, but nothing as of
yet. So, I'll keep an eye out and hope
something cool comes up.
>> Keep an eye out, man. Um, all right.
That's what I had for my live live
hacking events. Uh you know, chats and
takeaways. Um let's uh let's get into
some news content, shall we? First up on
the news, um actually we've got Gareth
Hayes dropping stuff as always. Um and
this one was particularly interesting, I
thought, y'all, because um he's using
this attributes. Uh uh for those of you
that are on YouTube, you can you can
check it out, but he's um using the
attributes
um reference inside of an HTML um on on
event handler. So he's got input on
focus and then attributes zero value. So
he's reassigning the first attribute of
the specific HTML element, which is in
fact the onfocus that he's presently in.
Um and then uh reassigning what
JavaScript should be run uh upon
execution of this uh function here. Um
and then he uses that to smuggle data in
from the uh hash which is contained in
the URL um reference uh and redefine
what the actual uh JavaScript is being
run when that one event handler occurs.
So, I know that that's a little bit a
little bit dense there, but the the the
main takeaways here that I think the the
hunter should have is that if you need
to smuggle data, maybe you've got like a
specific character set that you can't
get past, because this is pretty
character set liberal,
you can reassign attributes inside of uh
your HTML element. So input on focus or
whatever um
using the data from the URL um reference
which is only valid inside of an HTML
tag. Uh very brilliant approach here by
by Gareth. And I did have a little demo.
Um do do you understand what I'm saying
Grant or is this just like
>> Yeah. So for me like I'm looking at you
saying these words and I get like one
fifth of the context before my brain
goes nope. And then I get the other one
for like nope.
>> Okay, look at this. Look at this lab
really quickly because he linked this
lab as well. Okay, so the on click for
this input is attributes
>> zero. So the first attribute dot value
equals
>> um you know backtick plus URL plus
backtick. Okay, so essentially it's
saying hey take the current URL stick it
inside of the first attribute which is
the uncclick uh and put it inside of
template literal the back text. Right?
So then what you do is when you click
it, look what look what happens
>> now. It takes the current URL stick
sticks it inside of back ticks, right?
>> And then um from the hash you grab the
dollar sign curly brackets alert one
which allows you to execute code inside
of the template literal, right? And then
when you click it again, you get the
pop, right? So it's priming the data in
the hash you um with dollar sign curly
brackets alert one, right? And then it's
using the attributes zero value to to
take the data from the URL, stick it
inside of the the one event handler, and
then when you trigger it, it it triggers
the the actual code that's in the URL to
be run.
>> Yeah.
>> Right.
>> So, does he just sit at his desk and
goes, "You know what? I think this might
work." And then he just writes that and
it works. Like, how?
>> I think he does, dude. I think he
actually does do that.
Like I see some of these things on a
scroll on Twitter and I actually I laugh
out loud because I just think how has
someone just concocted that and
everything he posts is just so good.
>> It it's freaking good, man. And and I
will say for those of you that are not
like client side like loving client side
stuff, if you are, you should definitely
be investigating this. But
>> if you don't, your m major takeaways
here are using the attributes reference
to redefine attributes on your current
HTML tag
>> and then um knowing that URL the string
URL all caps is a way to reference
essentially the document URI um in only
when you are inside of an onvent
handler.
>> Doesn't it reference something else when
you're outside of a non-event handler
entirely? you just type URL, it doesn't
typically it's a it's like a it's like a
type, right? It's a constructor. But if
you're actually doing it inside of the
the function
>> um inside of like a onclick event or
something like that,
>> then okay. Well, it didn't update it
now, but yeah, you can see right here
that's the the document URI.
>> Nice,
>> right? Pretty cool stuff.
>> Yeah, he is he his brain needs to be
preserved and studied. It's just like
one of those things where crazy crazy
content continuously as well.
>> I'm with you. I'm with you. Definitely
Portzer Research. They've got some
amazing stuff coming out.
>> They do. On that note, Julie, he's had a
lot of love on the pod. They I should
say on the pod before um is back with
some more research which will help you
digest some of that Gareth's magic. Um,
>> really, really good write up, good blog.
And what I love about this and really
warms the heart upon opening. If you
have any thoughts on my blog and
articles you want to let me know, you
can either post a comment or tell me via
this feedback form. They are actively
looking for feedback from the community.
Is that not like such a
>> nice thing?
>> Has a feedback form on their free blog.
Dude,
>> that is that's just crazy. like that is
so nice of them to
>> that is such a commitment to quality.
>> Yeah. Yeah. So good. Um anyway, the
actual blog itself does a really nice
job of breaking down some of these more
exotic payloads uh that you might see
and exactly how some of these tag
template literals work.
>> Oh yeah. Yeah. Exactly. Just like we
were talking about just a second ago.
>> Exactly why they work and some of the
contexts that would be useful for them
to actually work in, which I thought was
really good. Um, I know again we've
mentioned so much of their research on
the blog before, but I really, really
like the way they break down every
single subject, give you every single
topic and give you some of the
applicable use cases as well
>> and just a really nice uh writing style
which I've grown an appreciation for
since the hacker notes, I must admit.
>> Yeah. Well, dude, I mean, I love this
one that you've got on the screen right
here, which is, you know, on error
equals eval and then throw equals alert
one. Like that's so fun. Like just being
able to use those error handlers and
then the throw keyword, it really allows
you to get around some some character
restrictions.
>> Yeah, it's like using your error message
as a uh as the payload, but then they
just keep breaking down these payloads
and how you can further eliminate
syntaxes that might be giving you a
problem.
>> Um really nice, useful if you have if
you're being blocked by a W, for
example. very useful if you're not as
comfortable with client side stuff like
me. Like this is the perfect content.
Um, and it probably builds upon some of
Gareth Hayes's content in his JavaScript
for hackers book which I have committed
to myself to read end to end. I always
get part of the way through and I'm like
this is some heavy stuff and never
commit to it. I will commit to it. I
will do it. Yeah, dude. That is
definitely one of the the seminal works,
you know, and in in making you a a good
client side hacker
>> 100%. And then the thing I did want to
give a shout out is like they give a
like the mother payload at the end. This
absolute I want to call it a
monstrosity, but it isn't. It's like
art. Um, just look at that. And it only
works in Chrome. And again, such a good
job of breaking it down exactly how it's
working. And
>> yeah, they've got they've got this is
without quotes it looks like. Wow.
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. They've they've abstracted away
the quotes with uh you know decimal
representation of strings and then
forcing a conversion with a uh looks
like with a reax there. That's uh that's
pretty sick,
>> bro. Honestly, it's just insane. So hats
off to them because every piece of
content they put out is just like so
in-depth, so in the weeds and overall
really good read.
>> Um, and then they give you a few key
points at the end. Commas can chain
multiple expressions returned in the
last one. Replacing the on error with
eval allows you to execute the error
messages code.
>> Errors thrown will become part of the
error message. And as long as you can
turn the error message into valid code,
you've succeeded.
>> Dude, that I I love that. Those four at
the end there, that's that's really
good. Okay, I'm gonna say them again.
Commas can chain multiple expressions,
returning the last one. That's pivotal
because uh you often will want to
control the return value while getting
something done, right? Replacing on air
with EVA allows you to execute the error
message as code. That's a a really good
one. Errors thrown will be a part of the
error message itself. So, converting the
error message into valid code. And then
as long as you can do that, you are
avoiding syntax errors in getting uh
your your payload through.
>> Yeah, dude. I feel like you should get
that as like a tattoo like the quote on
your arm for being a client side hack.
>> That's beautiful, man. For for um you
know, syntax or um uh character set
restricted environments, this is like
the new go-to.
>> Yeah. And they give you a lot of that
context throughout the blog post as
well. I can't think see where it is, but
exactly where it would be useful and why
it would be useful. So
>> worth the read for you guys which aren't
as handy on the client side as um as
like me really.
>> Yeah, good good stuff, man.
>> Um pivoting a little bit from uh well,
actually, you know what? Tell you what,
we'll we'll uh we'll stick with the
client side um stuff for just a second
longer. Uh, and I'm not going to spend
too much time and dwell on this one
because um it's not strictly relevant to
hacking.
>> Uh, but there is an amazing um
amazing write up here of Google's safe
content frame. And if you are at all
interested, if any of the listeners
here, I know a lot of you guys have absc
if your requirements for your company
require you know you to render an
arbitrary HTML file that is very hard to
do in a safe way. Um and you know
preserve isolation of code uh isolation
of your domain right because we can set
cookies at to the top level domain. Um
very difficult problem to solve. I have
spent a lot of time trying to crack safe
content frame that Google has produced
to to fix this problem. And uh it's it's
bulletproof, man. Like it is really
bulletproof.
>> Um and so if you're interested in
understanding how exactly all that works
um you can see how it works here. They
combine uh a a isolated domain with a
and a public suffix list uh registration
with um delivery via iframe that checks
event source and um blobs. And uh this
is the key part right here. The hashing
of the content uh and the parent origin
um to create a unique subdomain of these
domains uh which makes it impossible for
you to even like
you can't affect the code because the
parent origin changes and if the code
changes at all inside of it then it
changes the hash. So it's like
>> this is painful. Um, but really really
well done by the Google team and this is
I think the go-to solution if you have
to render untrusted HTML inside of your
app.
>> Now, is this a new thing or has this
been around for a while and they've just
improved upon it? The
>> it's it's been around for a while. This
is the first write up I've seen that
like fully explains the from the
engineering side, but there have been a
lot of CTFs run on it because the Google
team is like, "Hey, hack this." You
know?
>> Um, and yeah, it's pretty freaking
bulletproof. And I know that Terjank uh
who was mentioned in the last article
you you had up um was one of the main
engineers for this. Uh and it's just
it's freaking good, dude. It's really
really good.
>> Well, have the client side guys got
their hands on it? Jorian and co in the
channel. I'm sure they have.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I mean I I we've talked
about it before and I mean it's just
there there's just not much there's like
it painfully uses the right structure. I
mean that hashing that creates the
unique domain
>> and and you know having the public
suffix list
>> there's nothing you can do like that
just completely isolates everything. Um
so
>> one of those annoying ones. Will it pain
you as much as the coupe pad is did
>> um I don't know man. Coupe is coupe is
the worst. Coupe coupe is like really a
pain in my butt. Um,
>> the thing is even even if you can get a
frame reference to this thing, dude,
which is a problem in and of itself. Uh,
>> yeah, there's just nothing. There's no
attack surface. So,
>> yeah.
>> Yeah, I I I spent so much time. I was
like, you know what, guys? I'm gonna I'm
gonna assess this. And then the Tank was
over there laughing like, "All right,
bro. Like, take a stab at it." And I'm
like, "Dang,
>> nothing."
>> Yeah.
>> Oh, man. Yeah. Actually, I will say I
did find a problem with the
implementation of it somewhere though uh
in in Google's infrastructure. So,
>> well, that's something.
>> Yeah, there there's nothing wrong with
this itself, but the way that they took
this and implemented it was not spec and
so I was I was able to do something
there.
>> Oh, there you go. You're fine then. Um,
good stuff. I think the next one I'd
want to jump in on is a very very good
write up on Microsoft Entra. Let me just
share my screen.
>> Um, and there's a reason why I did want
to cover it because the depth that this
thing goes into is just insane. And
>> yeah, one token to rule them all.
Obtaining global admin in every Entra ID
tenant via actor tokens. Jesus.
>> Honestly, the reason I wanted to cover
this is because we've used the term mega
crit on the pod before and this is
literally an unstoppable mega crit that
they could have done nothing about
because there's no detection for it. Um,
so if people aren't familiar, Microsoft
Entra is essentially
uh Azure AD but the newer version
rehashed. Um, and it's pretty much their
cloud identity service. Um, so it can be
quite the target for a lot of red team
assessments
and the whole crux of the problem is
essentially you have I'll dive into the
impact in a minute. I just want to give
some context. You have these things
called actor tokens which are used by
some services to essentially um imitate
a user or service and do so with godlike
permissions in the sense that you can
use the service but not actually be the
user that initiated it. Um, so it also
uses the Microsoft Graph API and Azure
AD graph API which is somewhat
applicable to Bug Bountney because Bug
Bounty programs are run on both of them
as well. And this is the sort of content
that will help you attack those APIs
perfectly. Um, so the overview of the
actor tokens is that they were
essentially tokens issued by the access
control service. And this guy didn't
know what this service was, but he
guessed that it was a legacy thing used
by SharePoint applications. And uh, if
you've ever had an encounter with
SharePoint, you know it's it's pretty
awful. It's pretty pretty bad.
>> Always always a bad time.
>> Exactly. I was a SharePoint admin for uh
that was my first like real job in IT
was being a SharePoint admin and I did
not stay in that job for very long.
>> Yeah, no wonder you went to Bug Bounty
so quickly, mate. That is exactly dude.
That's tough. Um anyway, the whole way
this finding came about is that he was
examining an exchange flow and in this
exchange flow in a hybrid setup
essentially exchange would request an
actor token um when it wants to
communicate with another service. Now
the as I said earlier the actor token
allows it to imitate that service or
user that it's using and this is the the
overview of the token and for listeners
it is a JWT um but a lot of the claims
are gooids so they look like absolute
nonsense and unless you were really
deeply rooted into the ecosystem you
probably wouldn't have any idea what any
of these correspond to. Um, but luckily
this guy is so far embedded into this
ecosystem. He knew everything. Um, so
>> love to see it, man. Love to see that
dep
so many good pieces of information in
this and the breakdown. Um, and
essentially the audience and all the
claims are goods for what you're
requesting. And the main thing here
which is actually readable is the
trusted for delegation value which is
true and that is what allows the actor
token to be an actor token. Now in the
next part of the flow of this exchange
functionality I was looking at exchange
would embed the token that we just
covered in into an unsigned JWT which is
then sent to the resource provider which
was uh Azure graph. Now essentially
they've taken a wraps token which was
signed and then placed it in a
completely unwrapped um sorry unsigned
JWT. My bad
>> but they are using values from the
unsigned JWT to make um assumptions or
decisions based on the authentication of
that user.
Now don't know why they done that but
we'll carry on.
>> Why did they do that? The world will
never know.
>> Yeah. Why they done that? Who knows? Um,
now in the unsigned JWT, you have a name
ID which is originates from the Azure AD
graph API. Um, and more importantly, you
have the where is it? The
UPN. No, that one doesn't matter for
now. Um
now these impersonation tokens
especially all these claims specify the
service you want to impersonate and none
of them are signed. So once exchange has
that token it can use it to impersonate
anyone against the target service it
requested um for 24 hours by the way.
Now this is hilarious because and this
is taken directly from the blog. It
lacks almost every security control you
would want. There's no logs when dude
you can't skip the line before that. In
my personal opinion, this whole actor
token design is something that should
never have existed. Go ahead.
>> It lacks almost every security control
you'd want. There's no logs when act
tokens are issued. Since these services
can craft unsigned impersonation tokens
without talking to entraer, there are no
logs when they are created or used. They
cannot be pro re provoked. They
completely bypass any restrictions
configured in conditional access and we
have to rely on login from the re
resource provider. Now
this is just absolutely insane that
these sort of things are kicking about
in the
>> ecosystem and this next screenshot is
really sums it up. So you have the
signed actor token, but then the
unsigned JWT is what's actually being
used for some of the impersonation and
that is unsigned, which you can just put
whatever in, send it off, providing you
have that signed actor token.
>> Wow. So, okay. So, yeah, that's really
weird. It looks like we're for the audio
listeners, we're looking at the
breakdown of a JWT. So you see the
header right in the close uh parenthesis
and then you're looking at the body and
you see inside of that JDT uh a field
called actor token which contains a sign
JWT but then you also see following that
a bunch of fields that you would expect
to see in the in the JWT AUD is uh ISS
etc. And these this is an unsigned token
and then I guess it's using those values
from the unsigned JDBT rather than the
signed JWT inside of the unsigned JBT.
Is that am I representing that right?
>> Yeah, exactly that. So you've got two
different checks being performed. You've
got the first check which actually gives
you the actor token to make sure it's
valid and you're requesting something
valid, but then they go ahead and wrap
that in an unsigned JWT and make
assumptions based off of what you want
to assume on the unsigned JWT.
>> Okay, okay, Brandon, let let me let me
ask you this here. I'm sorry to
interrupt because I know this is a
complex bug, but I think what might be a
good like global takeaway here for us is
that if we see a JWT that contains
another JWT,
>> look at the the fields that are shared
between the two because I I mean I could
totally see how this would happen,
right? Essentially, they are looking at
the top level JDT instead of the
embedded one. And all they needed, you
know, to maybe to fix their code even
was, you know, dot here, scroll up a
little bit. What's the name of that?
Yeah, a dot actor token. AUD, right?
Rather than a AUD, right? So, if there's
any embed and then overlap in the body
of those JWT tokens, that could be a
really good area for us to test.
>> Absolutely. And I feel like as well this
blog for me summarizes perfectly when
you're looking at a target with so many
interconnected and interacting services
that depends on another service to
perform its authentication for example
and completely trust that that it is the
absolute truth. There's so much gold in
that, man. Especially when you have two
different APIs kicking around. Like one
of these APIs is actually only there and
being phased out and it's there for
backwards compatibility issues and
there's been so many bugs come off the
back of it. And yeah, like the whole
write up very very good. It covers the
practical abuse this exact impact. It
could basically use a token from its own
tenant to go cross tenant and
impersonate anyone using publicly
available ids of which aren't um even
though they are GU IDs in some instances
they're not secret you can retrieve them
and if you've ever looked at any of the
Azure or Microsoft bug bounty program
you will know that there are so many
ways to disclose some of this
information I know quite a few hunters
on there
>> yeah dude it says okay find the net ID
of a regular user craft after the
impersonation, use that impersonation to
list all global admins on the tenant and
get their net ID and then impersonate
those and then do whatever the heck you
want. That's that's nasty, man. That's
super nasty.
>> Crazy. And if you are thinking about
attacking some of these services, start
off with this blog because it gives you
exactly where and how to find some of
these net ids and even some of the
impacts of the threat model when you are
looking at cross tenant interenant um
and also using the actual APIs and we
could talk about this right up for about
an hour. So I will try and wrap it up
because there is so much content packed
into here. But the last thing I did want
to cover they've got detections and
everything like that is this last bit
here. the very last part of the blog. I
do not have access to any tenants in a
national cloud deployment. So I was not
able to test whether the vulnerability
existed there. Since national cloud
deployments use their own uh token
signing keys, it's unlikely that it
would have been possible to execute this
attack from a tenant in the public cloud
to one of these national clouds. I do
consider it likely that this attack
would have worked across tenants in the
same national cloud deployment. That
level of understanding and expertise on
a service is like master level. And
whenever this person now brings out a
blog or any content about Entra, Azure
graph or anything related, I will trust
them. Absolutely. Because you don't get
this this sort of information just by
playing around with these things. You
spend a serious amount of time to
understand that.
>> Yeah, dude. I'm going to just click on
their ex directly from uh this article
and yeah, dang it. I'm not following
them. I've been missing out. I'm going
to turn on notifications. That's pretty
sick.
>> Yeah. So good, man. So good.
>> I love that you read that little little
line. This is like a grayed out line at
the very bottom in the like subnotes as
well, Brandon, at the bottom. So, props
to you for for being very thorough in
your assessment of uh this writeup. And
I think that also is a is a vote of
confidence you know to hear this
researcher say that for me in in sort of
um nation segmented cloud environments
right where you know you'll have like
you know US government AWS or whatever
or you know that sort of thing sort of
segmented off I was like uh in the past
I've been like okay that might be a
little bit overboard you know
bureaucracy saying okay everything's got
to be segmented
>> but it's cool to see that such an
impactful vulnerability like this
actually you know it was limited by that
sort of nationbased cloud segmentation
if if I'm understanding what he's saying
correctly.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Absolutely. And I feel like
it sums up perfectly once you have so
much context in some of these ser um
services. You can really dig deep into
the threat model to the extent that you
can understand whether deployment
locations and these more segregated
environments would be affected by
knowing that they use their own token
signing keys. Like honestly, hats off to
this guy. It's very commendable the
depth and level of research that they've
done on this one. Very, very good.
>> Totally, man. Totally. That's uh d I
km.io.
So definitely check that out if you guys
want to um add that to like your RSS
list or whatever. Um next up, a little
bit lighter, uh we've got Flarerocks. Uh
Firerox is actually one of the tools I
use very often. Uh despite that episode
with uh with um uh Ryan from uh you
know, Akami saying like, "Hey, Justin,
that's illegal. Don't do that. That
breaks the terms and uh and services or
whatever." Um, so anyway, if you're
looking to not do that, then do it
through Cloudflare instead.
[Laughter]
Oh man,
>> with flare procs um uh and get, you
know, essentially for those of you that
aren't familiar with it, essentially
this abuses, um sort of ephemeral cloud
environments like workers and um I guess
like you API gateway in the AWS one um
to get you new IPs for every single
request. So if you're dealing with a uh
strong amount of rate limiting and you
really need fuzz, then you're going to
want to use fireox or flare prox to do
that. Um, and that is uh this one is has
popped up um that uses the Cloudflare IP
space to avoid detections and blocks.
>> Yeah. And the code looks pretty solid. I
mean uh I will say one that that's a
little bit weird with this. I know that
Fireprox gives you um a unique domain
for each host that you want to fuzz.
Mhm.
>> It looks like this one actually just
allows you to specify
a URL equals in your um
>> like quer parameter of your target,
right? So it's like this one there might
be some weird encoding stuff with that
or some weird gotchas there. Um so I
would keep an eye out for that. Uh, and
it certainly I mean it looks like it's
passing through all your put and posts
and all that sort of thing, but it does
allow you to be a little bit more
flexible is you can keep that worker up
and use it to scan multiple different
hosts if you want. So
>> yeah, more importantly, absolutely do
not host that on a very guessable domain
or something you use a lot because if
that's your O equals and it accepts
anything, I'll dig into the code later,
but that that's ripe for abuse. So yeah,
be careful on that front as well.
>> Yeah, I think this sort of a spin up
spin down as you as you do, you know,
thing. But yeah, it's true. If you
forget to spin it down, that could be
that could be, you know, you could be
paying for a lot of people's brute
forces out there.
>> Yeah, I feel like as well now we're
starting to get to the point where a lot
of these ecosystems like when Firerox
got released, right, AWS was really I
think off the top of my head one of the
only ecosystems that supported it with
the API gateways. We're now seeing a lot
of other providers mature up until the
point that they have like a competitor
service offering. So now you've got
these tools coming out and when you
combine it with um asset notes new town
you go right okay I'm accessible from
Cloudflare's IP range or I'm accessible
for AWS I've got that test sorted let's
just spin one up here and you can have a
lot of fun with it I think so
>> it's quite nice to see how it's all
playing out over time now that we're
just bypassing all these silly defenses
that people are putting out there.
>> Yeah. Yeah. And and I mean there's
definitely a little gray area with the
you know agreements or terms of services
with these but hackers going to hack. So
>> yeah we'll get our accounts banned but
>> yeah and I'm when that came up on the
episode I was like okay you s I guess
you have to say that as an employee but
come on man a motivated attacker will
not give an absolute hell about that.
>> Yeah and that's what I told him too. I
was like, "Look, man, we're all on the
same side here, you know, like as much
as it feels like maybe sometimes we
aren't, we are, you know."
>> Yeah.
>> Um, so
>> yeah, I think I Yeah, I agree.
>> No, 100%. Um, how are we doing on time?
Are we okay?
>> Yeah, we're good. Um, let me let me just
uh I'll I'll do this next one real quick
and then we'll we'll wrap it. That cool?
>> Sure.
>> Okay. So, um, just wanted to give a
shout out because, uh, I Tugalo, who is
an excellent hacker, um,
did a writeup recently, um, on Kaido
101. And if you read his blog, which I
do and all of you guys should as well,
um he credits his shift to Kaido, I
think with a lot of growth for him as a
hacker, uh as somebody who was um you
know, previously up and cominging in the
space and I think now is pretty
confirmed uh top tier hacker. Um and so
he was talking about his shift to Kaido
and he wrote this Kaido 101, how to
master it write up. Um and he breaks
down uh coming from Burp some friction
points you might see um CLI versus
desktop breaks down all the various
sections of the Kaido application
understanding concepts like uh HTTPQL
workflows plugins uh etc. Um, so if any
of you guys are looking to take the deep
dive on Kaido and are looking to be led
to the light, so to speak, here, uh, I'm
looking at you, Brandon, uh, then this
could be a good read for you guys to
kind of understand exactly how to do
that.
>> Nice. Yeah, these sort of resources, I
feel like when you're very much stuck in
your ways, like I have been in Bert for
forever, those are the sort of resources
you want to find just to understand the
capabilities, what you can do. And on
that note, the Kaido scope, I messaged
you about it during that event, but man,
please can that get changed really fast.
>> It is. It is. So, Kaido Kaido um has a
public issue tracker.
>> Okay.
>> And you can go to the road map and one
of the items on the road map right now
is is try to adjust the scope to be a
little bit more compatible with hacker
expectations.
>> Oh man, I will I will fund my
hard-earned British pound coins to get
that implemented into the tool if I have
to. I need it because it was giving me a
few problems in this event. It's I guess
because of the current transition over.
>> Yeah, man. It to be honest like I get
it, but I use filters and it just works,
you know, like that's what I use and and
it works fine. So, it is a little bit of
a friction point. It's definitely not as
intuitive, but there are there is a
solution. You know, you can do path path
based filtering and very granular
filtering on what you want to see in HTP
history using filters rather than scope.
But that right there is the key. What
you just said, you can use HTTP filters.
Now, there's a lot of extensions which
solely rely on the scope. So, your
extension is absolutely hammered with
everything when
>> cuz I was seeing this mismatch because I
did have a filter on, but then my
extension was going haywire. And I was
thinking, what is going on? And it's
because it uses the scope. So,
>> in scope.
>> Yeah.
>> Interesting. All right. Good, good
feedback, man. I'll bring that to the
team right after this episode.
>> Awesome. I'll fund it as well to get it
pushed out if you want.
>> Great. I'll let him know. Thanks, man.
All right, that's a wrap. That's the
pod. Peace. Peace. And that's a wrap on
this episode of Critical Thinking.
Thanks so much for watching to the end,
y'all. If you want more critical
thinking content, uh, or if you want to
support the show, head over to
ctbb.show/isord.
You can hop in the community. There's
lots of great highlevel hacking
discussion happening there on top of
masterclasses, hackalongs, exclusive
content, and a full-time hunters guild
if you're a full-time hunter. It's a
great time. Trust me. All right, I'll
see you there.